

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

## **ABOUT ME**

I'm an ambitious and driven individual. I like challenges. I'm always looking for opportunity to do better and grow. I'm humble and i want learn new skills for improve myself. I worked in two companies, for about three years overall, where i learned how to work in a team, how to organize my tasks and how to manage problems.

### **SKILLS**

Javascript HTML & CSS React C#

### **LANGUAGES**

English: B1 Certificate Italian: Native

#### CONTACTS

Telephone number: +39 3402136572

Website (portfolio): www.edoardovincenzi.it

Email:

edoardo.vincenzi95@gmail.com

Linkedin: <u>@edoardo-vincenzi</u>

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Web developer

Enerj srl (01/2021 - 09/2021)

- Analyse software specifications
- Implement front-end website design
- Computer programming
- Develop and Software maintenance
- Debug software
- Web programming
- Use software libraries
- .NET
- JavaScript
- HTML
- CSS
- Razor HTML
- Postgres SQL

#### **ICT** system developer

Archiva Srl (06/2017 - 03/2019)

- Design, develop and distribute applications for mission-critical systems
- Software: Informatica Data Transformation Studio
- Software: Altova MapForce for mapping source system data (xml files, flat files, csv, edifact) to data warehouse tables
- Knowledge basic of SQL Server, Oracle, DB2, MariaDB for SQL programming

#### **EDUCATION**

# **University of Verona**

Bachelor's degree Computer Science (10/2014 - 12/2020)

First / second year

Basic mathematical and physical skills

Basic computer skills:

- Programming and algorithms
- Computer architectures, operating systems and computer networks

Second / third year Additional specific skills:

- Databases and information systems
- Fundamentals of information technology
- Programming languages
- Compilers
- Advanced programming techniques
- Computer graphics

### Start2Impact

#### **Front End Development Student**

HTML & CSS

Javascript base & advance

React

### **INTERESTS AND HOBBY**

I love reading fantasy and personal growth books.

i love going to gym.

I love studying a new technology and programming.